Guide to Barbara Sloan European Union Document Collection, 1951-2004 EUDC
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- POLICY AREA, II.
  - CUSTOMS UNION, 6.
    - CUSTOMS LEGISLATION - General
      - Customs Relief Systems [443.112.10], 1986-1994; 3.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 183)
      - Customs Territory [443.112.2], 1968-2002; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 182)
      - Free Zones [443.112.3], 1967-2002; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 182)
      - Origin of Products [443.112.4], 1967-2004; 6.; 2 folders 8" (Box 182)
      - Bonded Warehouse & Bonded Goods [443.112.5], 1967-1996; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 183)
      - Customs Debt [443.112.6], 1976-2000; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 183)
      - Customs - End Use [443.112.7], 1977-1979; 9.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 183)
      - Temporary Import Arrangements [443.112.8], 1978-2001; 10.; 1 folder 3" (Box 183)
      - Counterfeit Goods [443.112.9], 1994-2003; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 183)
    - TARIFF ECONOMY - General
      - Tariff Economy - General [443.113], 1968-2003; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 183)
      - Tariff Quotas & Temporary Reductions in Duty General [443.113.1], 1960-1998; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 183)
      - Tariff Quotas & Temporary Reductions in Duty Specific Products [443.113.2], 1960-2003; 3.; 2 folders 9" (Box 184)
      - Customs Duty, Temporary Increases in [443.113.3], 1969-1991; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 184)
      - Taxes Equivalent to Customs Duties [443.114], 1960-2000; 5.; 1 folder 3" (Box 184)
    - PROCESSING
      - Inward Processing [443.115], 1958-2000; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 185)
      - Inward Processing Agricultural Products [443.115.1], 1964-2003; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 185)
      - Outward Processing [443.116], 1970-1998; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 185)
    - CIRCULATION OF MERCHANDISE - General
      - Circulation of Merchandise - General [443.12], 1962-2003; 1.; 2 folders 8" (Box 185)
      - Euronorms [443.122.2], 1958-1986; 2.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 186)
      - Measures Equivalent to Quantitative Restrictions Border Formalities [443.123], 1967-2000; 3.; 3 folders 11" (Box 186)
      - Circulation of Merchandise Forms [443.125], 1969-2003; 4.; 1 folder 4" (Box 187)
      - Travellers Allowances [443.126], 1985-2002; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 188)
  - DEVELOPMENT - aid for AASM/ACP, 7.
    - DEVELOPMENT AID FOR AASM & ACP. General
      - DEVELOPMENT AID FOR ASSOCIATION OF AFRICAN STATES AND MALAGASY (AASM) AND AFRICAN-CARIBBEAN-PACIFIC (ACP). General [448], 1960-1996; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 281)
      - ACP, Training Programs Scholarships [448.12], 1963-1986; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 281)
      - ACP, Country Profiles [448.13], 1994; 3.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 281)
      - ACP, Countries Associated with Member States [448.14], 1959-1994; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 281)
      - Netherlands Antilles [448.14(115)], 1962-1993; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 281)
      - Surinam [448.14(142)], 1968-1984; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 281)
      - African Associates & Madagascar [448.14(501)], 7.; 1 folder (Box 283)
    - OVERSEAS DEPARTMENTS & TERITORIES
      - Overseas Departments & Territories [448.14(502)(503)], 1958-2003; 1.; 3 folders 13" (Box 282)
      - Canary Islands [448.141(205)], 1985-2003; 2.; 1 folder 3" (Box 281)
      - Ceuta [448.141(205)], 1985-2003; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 281)
      - Melilla [448.141(205)], 1985-2003; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 281)
      - Greenland [448.141(401)], 1983-2001; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 281)
    - CONVENTIONS
      - AASM (First Convention) Preparatory Phase PART 1 [448.141(501)], 1959-1962; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 287)
      - AASM (Second Convention) Preparatory Phase PART 2 [448.141(501)], 1960-1962; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 287)
      - AASM (Second Convention) Ratification Phase PART 2A [448.141(501)], 1963-1964; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 287)
      - AASM (Second Convention) Implementation PART 2B [448.141(501)], 1964-1969; 4.; 1 folder 2" (Box 287)
      - AASM (Second Convention) Activity Reports PART 2C [448.141(501)], 1965-1969; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 287)
      - AASM (Third Convention) Preparatory Phase PART 3 [448.141(501)], 1966-1985; 6.; 1 folder 3" (Box 287)
      - AASM (Third Convention) Implementation PART 3A [448.141(501)], 1970-1972; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 287)
      - AASM (Third Convention) Activity Reports PART 3B [448.141(501)], 1973-1984; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 286)
      - ACP (Fourth Convention) Implementation PART 4A [448.141(501)], 1975-1988; 9.; 1 folder 3" (Box 286)
      - ACP (Fifth Convention) Preparatory Phase PART 5 [448.141(501)], 1976-1980; 10.; 1 folder 4" (Box 285)
      - ACP (Fourth Convention) Preparatory Phase PART 4 [448.141(501)], 1976-1995; 11.; 2 folders 8" (Box 286)
      - ACP (Fifth Convention) Implementation PART 5A [448.141(501)], 1980-1986; 12.; 1 folder 6" (Box 285)
      - ACP (Sixth Convention) Preparatory Phase PART 6 [448.141(501)], 1984-1990; 13.; 1 folder 5" (Box 284)
      - ACP (Sixth Convention) Implementation PART 6A [448.141(501)], 1985-1989; 14.; 1 folder 4" (Box 284)
      - ACP (Eighth Convention) Preparatory Phase Part 8 [448.141(501)], 1997-2003; 15.; 1 folder 3" (Box 283)
      - ACP (Eighth Convention) Implementation PART 8A [448.141(501)], 2001-2003; 16.; 1 folder 1" (Box 283)
      - ACP (Seventh Convention) Preparatory Phase PART 7 [448.141(50l)], 1988-1990; 17.; 1 folder 2" (Box 283)
      - ACP (Seventh Convention) Implementation PART 7A [448.141(50l)], 1988-2000; 18.; 1 folder 5" (Box 283)
    - EUROPEAN DEVELOPMENT FUND
      - European Development Fund, General [448.3], 1959-2003; 1.; 6 folders 24" (Box 288)
      - European Development Fund, Programs [448.31] (Folder Missing), 1977-2003; 2.; 1 folder (Box 289)
      - European Development Fund, Technical Operations [448.32], 1977-1998; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 290)
      - European Development Fund, Financial Operations [448.33], 1977-1982; 4.; 1 folder 2" (Box 290)
      - European Development Fund, Status Reports 1969 [448.34], 1959-1962; 5.; 3 folders 7" (Box 290)
    - TRADE
      - ACP, Trade & Production [448.4], 1970-1994; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 290)
      - ACP, Trade Liberalization & Promotion [448.41], 1973-1997; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 290)
      - Origin of Products - ACP [448.411], 1964-1988; 3.; 1 folder 4" (Box 291)
      - ACP, Products, Organizations of Markets Production Aids [448.42], 1969-2003; 4.; 1 folder 5" (Box 291)
      - Sugar, ACP and Association d'outre mer. Overseas Association (AOM) [448.421], 1977-2003; 5.; 1 folder 4" (Box 291)
      - Beef and Veal, ACP & Association d'outre mer. Overseas Association (AOM) [448.422], 1975-2003; 6.; 2 folders 1" (Box 292)
      - Bananas + Dollar Zone Bananas, ACP & Association d'outre mer. Overseas Association (AOM) [448.423], 1982-2002; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 292)
    - COMMODITY SUPPORT
      - Stabex [448.43], 1980-2001; 1.; 1 folder 5" (Box 292)
      - Sysmin [448.44], 1979-2001; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 292)
    - SPECIAL AGENCIES
      - Centre for Industrial Development & Industrial Committee [448.5], 1977-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 292)
      - Technical Center for Agricultural & Rural Cooperation [448.6], 1986 & 1987; 2.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 292)
  - DISSEMINATION OF INFORMATION, 8.
    - Dissemination of Information-General [4413], 1960-1997; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 312)
    - Industrial Property, Patents, Dissemination of research results [4413.1], 1966-2000; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 312)
    - Committee for Information & Documentation on Science and Technology [4413.31], 1973-1991; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 312)
    - European Computer Program Library [4413.32], 1972-1991; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 312)
    - Information & Documentation Center (CID) [4413.2], 1964-1984; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 312)
  - ECONOMIC & FINANCIAL AFFAIRS, 9.
    - ECONOMIC & FINANCIAL AFFAIRS General
      - ECONOMIC & FINANCIAL AFFAIRS General [442], 1960-2003; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 166)
      - Economic Research Institute [442.12], 1975-1993; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 168)
      - Medium-Term Economic Policy Committee and Programs [442.11], 1963-2003; 3.; 2 folders 6" (Box 168)
      - Short-Term Economic Policy Committee & Programs [442.221], 1964-2001; 4.; 2 folders 5" (Box 170)
      - Economic Policy Committee [442.316], 1974-2003; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 174)
    - ECONOMIC SITUATION
      - Economic Situation Quarterly & Annual Report [442.1], 1962-2003; 1.; 5 folders 23" (Box 166, Box 167, Box 168)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Benelux [442.22(24)], 1967-2003; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 168)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Germany [442.22(42)], 1969-2003; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 168)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Austria [442.22(44)], 2000-2002; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Spain [442.22(47)], 1985-2003; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Finland [442.22(48)], 1998-2003; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends France [442.22(49)], 1962-2003; 7.; 1 folder 4" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends United Kingdom [442.22(51)], 1976-2003; 8.; 1 folder 2" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Greece [442.22(53)], 1981-2003; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Ireland [442.22(55)], 1976-2003; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Italy [442.22(57)], 1974-2003; 11.; 1 folder 2" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Portugal [442.22(62)], 1986-2003; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends Denmark [442.22(66)], 1974-2003; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 169)
      - Economy & Economic Trends, Sweden [442.22(68)], 1999-2003; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 169)
    - MONETARY DEVELOPMENTS
      - European Monetary System (EMS) General [442.31], 1968-2003; 1.; 7 folders 29" (Box 170, Box 171, Box 172)
      - Currency Exchange Problems - Internal Balance of Payments [442.314], 1971-2000; 2.; 1 folder 4" (Box 173)
      - Currency Exchange Problems & Agriculture [442.314(A)], 1971-2003; 3.; 4 folders 10" (Box 173)
      - Euro [442.33], 1988-2003; 4.; 2 folders 6" (Box 175)
      - Unit of Account European Currency Unit ECU [332.453.1], 1964-1994; 5.; 2 folders 5" (Box 10)
      - International Money - European Currency [332.43], 1961-1986; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 10)
      - Monetary Committee [435.1], 1961-1998; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 90)
      - European Monetary Cooperation Fund [442.315], 1973-2003; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 174)
      - European Monetary Institute [442.318], 1993-2002; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 174)
      - European Central Bank [442.319], 1998-2003; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 174)
      - Central Bankers Committee [442.311], 1970-2003; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 172)
      - Meetings of Finance Ministers [442.312], 1962-1994; 12.; 1 folder (Box 172)
    - CAPITAL
      - Capital Movements [442.313], 1962-2003; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 172)
      - Capital Markets: Europe [332.6(20)], 1963-2000; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 11)
    - BALANCE OF PAYMENTS
      - Balance of Payments Loans, European Community [442.317], 1976-2002; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 174)
      - Balance of Payments - International, & EC Role in and its Effect on EC [332.453.23], 1966-1991; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 11)
    - NATIONAL BUDGETS
      - National Budgets & Public Finance [442.32], 1961-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 174)
      - Budget Policy Committee & Programs [442.321], 1965-1978; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 174)
    - INVESTMENT
      - Foreign Investment in EEC Countries [332.67(25) C], 1965-2001; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 12)
      - Domestic Investment of EEC Countries [332.67(25) A], 1961-1997; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 11)
      - Foreign Investment of EEC Countries [332.67(25) B], 1969-2001; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 11)
      - Foreign Investment in Developing Countries [332.67(4)], 1964-1996; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 11)
  - ENERGY, 10.
    - ENERGY General [4417], 1964-2002; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 353)
    - Coal [4417.3], 1953-2003; 2.; 4 folders 16" (Box 359)
    - Electricity [4417.52], 1961-2003; 3.; 1 folder 6" (Box 362)
    - Energy Economy [4417.2], 1966-2003; 4.; 1 folder 4" (Box 358)
    - Energy Forecasts; Balance Sheets; Studies [4417.22], 1968-1998; 5.; 1 folder 5" (Box 358)
    - Energy Policy [4417.1], 1968-2004; 6.; 7 folders 25" (Box 353, Box 354, Box 355)
    - Energy Research Programs [4417.12], 1975-2003; 7.; 5 folders 23" (Box 356, Box 357)
    - Energy Structure (contains items on Trans-European Network-Energy - [T-ENs_Energy]) [4417.21], 1969-2003; 8.; 1 folder 2" (Box 358)
    - Gas [4417.42], 1960-2004; 9.; 2 folders 5" (Box 361)
    - Hydrocarbons [4417.4], 1966-2003; 10.; 2 folders 5" (Box 360)
    - Nuclear Energy & Electricity, General [4417.5], 1970-1993; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 362)
    - Nuclear Energy [4417.51], 1967-2003; 12.; 2 folders 4" (Box 362)
    - Oil Bulletin [4417.411] (folder missing), 13. (Box 361)
    - Petroleum & Petroleum Products [4417.41], 1960-2003; 14.; 4 folders 13" (Box 360)
  - ENLARGEMENT, 11.
    - Enlargement First UK Denmark Ireland Norway [441.21], 1967-1982; 1.; 3 folders 10" (Box 164, Box 97)
    - EFTA, Negotiations with Non-Applicant States Beginning June 1971 [441.212], 1956-2003; 2.; 3 folders 20" (Box 164, Box 97, Box 98)
    - Enlargement Second Third Greece Spain Portugal [441.213], 1979-1987; 3.; 2 folders 8" (Box 164, Box 99)
    - Enlargement Fourth Post 1992 [441.214], 1994-2001; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 164, Box 99)
    - Enlargement Fifth Post 1994 [441.215], 1997-2003; 5.; 2 folders 10" (Box 164, Box 100)
    - Enlargement: Weekly Newsletter [441.215A], 2000-2003; 6.; 1 folder 3" (Box 164, Box 100)
    - Wider Europe Debate 2003- [441.216], 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 165, Box 100)
  - ENVIRONMENT - European Communities, 12.
    - Pollution, General [628], 1970-2003; 1.; 9 folders 43" (Box 391, Box 392, Box 393, Box 394, Box 395)
    - Air Pollution [628.53], 1968-2003; 2.; 3 folders 15" (Box 399, Box 400)
    - Dust Pollution [628.511], 1968-1983; 3.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 398)
    - Eco Label [628.52], 1990-2003; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 399)
    - Environmental Audits [628.02], 1992-2003; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 396)
    - Environmental Impact Assessment [628.03], 1991-2003; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 396)
    - Environmental Research & Studies [628.001.5], 1978-2001; 7.; 2 folders 6" (Box 395)
    - European Environment Agency [628.01], 1984-2003; 8.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 395)
    - Greenhouse Effect, Meteorology, climate change [551.5], 1973-2004; 9.; 2 folders 8" (Box 379)
    - Nature & Wildlife Protection [502.7], 1968-2003; 10.; 4 folders 15" (Box 378)
    - Noise Pollution [628.517], 1976-2003; 11.; 1 folder 4" (Box 399)
    - Oceanography [551.46], 1969-1997; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 379)
    - Polluter Pays Principle [628.04], 1997-2003; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 396)
    - Soil Pollution [628.516], 2002-2003; 14.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 398)
    - Waste Policy Recycling Disposal [628.54], 1986-2003; 15.; 2 folders 11" (Box 401)
    - Water, General [628.1], 1975-2003; 16.; 1 folder 3" (Box 396)
    - Water Pollution [628.19], 1967-2003; 17.; 4 folders 23" (Box 396, Box 397, Box 398)
  - EXTERNAL RELATIONS, 13.
    - External Relations - General [441], 1959-2002; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 95)
    - INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATIONS
      - International Organizations & Protocol [441.1], 1958-1993; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 95)
      - International Atomic Energy Agency [469.2], 1959-2003; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 374)
      - International Monetary Fund. EU Relations with [441.1: 332.152.1], 1961-1998; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 95)
      - United Nations. EU Relations with [441.1: 40], 1974-2003; 4.; 2 folders 7" (Box 95)
      - United Nations, Law of the Sea [341.225], 1972-1998; 5.; 1 folder 5" (Box 19)
      - International Labour Organization [441.1: 412], 1964-2001; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 96)
      - Food and Agricultural Organization & World Food Council [441.1: 413], 1974-2003; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 96)
      - UNESCO, EU Relations with [441.1: 414], 1965-1993; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 96)
      - World Health Organization [441.1: 417], 1989-2003; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 96)
      - OECD (and OEEC), EU Relations with [441.1: 480], 1968-1994; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 96)
      - NATO, EU Relations with [441.1: 488.8], 1971; 1973; 1978; 11.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 96)
      - UNCTAD 1964 [411.21], 1964-1967; 12.; 1 folder 3" (Box 41)
      - UNCTAD 1968 [411.22], 1968-1973; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 41)
      - UNCTAD 1972 [411.23], 1972-1975; 14.; 1 folder 2" (Box 41)
      - UNCTAD 1976 [411.24], 1976-1979; 15.; 1 folder 2" (Box 41)
      - UNCTAD 1979 [411.25], 1979-1985; 16.; 1 folder 2" (Box 41)
      - UNCTAD 1983 [411.26], 1983-1999; 17.; 1 folder 1" (Box 42)
      - UNIDO [419.6], 1980-1984; 18.; 1 folder 1" (Box 47)
    - DIPLOMATIC RELATIONS
      - Community Diplomatic Corps [341.7], 1966-1999; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 20)
      - Visits of Community Officials - Miscellaneous [441.11], 1967-1993; 2.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 96)
      - Visits to Community Miscellaneous [441.12], 1971-2002; 3.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 96)
      - Diplomatic Missions to the Community [441.13], 1961-2003; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 96)
      - Diplomatic Missions of the Community [441.14], 1975-2001; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 96)
      - European Agency for Cooperation (EAC) [441.141], 1978-1986; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 96)
    - DEVELOPING COUNTRIES General
      - Developing Countries General, 1961-2003; 1.; 8 folders 21"
      - Developing Countries [441.2(4)], 1961-2003; 2.; 9 folders 26" (Box 106, Box 107, Box 108)
      - Generalized Preferences System Closures [441.2(4)A], 1997-1998; 3.; 1 folder 4" (Box 109)
      - Generalized Preferences System General [441.2(4)B], 1966-2003; 4.; 6 folders 26" (Box 109, Box 110, Box 111)
      - Stabex for Least Developed Countries [441.2(4)C], 1986-1989; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 111)
      - North/South Conference [480.71], 1975-1990; 6.; 2 folders 6" (Box 375)
      - Food Aid [339.6: 63], 1963-2002; 7.; 7 folders 30" (Box 16, Box 17, Box 18)
    - COUNTRIES & GROUPS OF COUNTRIES
      - Countries & Groups of Countries [441.2], 1969-2002; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 96)
      - Canada [441.2(102)], 1960-2003; 2.; 4 folders 13" (Box 135)
      - United States [441.2(103)], 1963-2003; 3.; 24 folders 94" (Box 136, Box 137, Box 138, Box 139, Box 140, Box 141, Box 142, Box 143, Box 144, Box 145)
      - Commonwealth [441.2(52)] (Years 1982-1990 Missing), 1960-2003; 4.; 3 folders 12" (Box 118)
    - LATIN AMERICA & CARIBBEAN
      - Latin America & Caribbean [441.2(132)], 1962-2002; 1.; 6 folders 14" (Box 146, Box 147)
      - Andean Pact [441.2(147)], 1982-2003; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 149)
      - Mercosur [441.2(148)], 1994-2003; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 149)
      - Argentina [441.2(134)], 1966-2003; 4.; 1 folder 5" (Box 148)
      - Bolivia [441.2(135)], 1977-2003; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 148)
      - Brazil [441.2(136)], 1964-2003; 6.; 1 folder 4" (Box 148)
      - Chile [441.2(137)], 1974-2003; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 148)
      - Columbia [441.2(138)], 1976-2003; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 148)
      - Costa Rica [441.2(110)], 2002; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 146)
      - Cuba [441.2(119)], 1978-2003; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 146)
      - Ecuador [441.2(139)], 1991-2002; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 148)
      - El Salvador [441.2(112)], 1980-2003; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 146)
      - Guatemala [441.2(106)], 1978-2003; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 146)
      - Honduras [441.2(107)], 1977-2003; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 146)
      - Mexico [441.2(104)], 1973-2003; 15.; 1 folder 5" (Box 145)
      - Nicaragua [441.2(132)], 1978-2003; 16.; 1 folder 1" (Box 146)
      - Panama [441.2(111)], 2000-2003; 17.; 1 folder 1" (Box 146)
      - Paraguay [441.2(143)], 1964-2003; 18.; 1 folder 1" (Box 149)
      - Peru [441.2(144)], 1971-2003; 19.; 1 folder 1" (Box 149)
      - Uruguay [441.2(145)], 1970-2002; 20.; 1 folder 2" (Box 149)
      - Venezuela [441.2(146)] (folder missing), 21.; 1 folder (Box 149)
    - MEDITERRANEAN & MIDDLE EAST
      - Mediterranean Countries [441.2(6)], 1970-2004; 1.; 3 folders 17" (Box 111)
      - Euro-Arab Dialogue [441.2(6)A], 1976-1994; 2.; 1 folder 3" (Box 112)
      - Gulf Cooperation Council [441.2(6)B], 1991-2002; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 112)
      - Algeria (See Also 441.2(254) Tunisia) [441.2(211)], 1963-2003; 4.; 1 folder 5" (Box 149)
      - Egypt [441.2(220)], 1972-2003; 5.; 1 folder 7" (Box 150)
      - Morocco (See Also 441.2(254) Tunisia) [441.2(234)], 1965-2003; 6.; 2 folders 8" (Box 150)
      - Tunisia (Maghreb Filed Here) [441.2(254)], 1958-2003; 7.; 3 folders 10" (Box 151)
      - Iran [441.2(324)], 1983-2003; 8.; 1 folder 3" (Box 157)
      - Iraq [441.2(323)], 1991-2004; 9.; 1 folder 3" (Box 157)
      - Israel [441.2(325)], 1963-1999; 10.; 3 folders 13" (Box 158)
      - Jordan [441.2(320)], 1977-2003; 11.; 1 folder 4" (Box 156)
      - Lebanon [441.2(327)], 1987-2003; 12.; 1 folder 6" (Box 161)
      - Palestine [441.2(325.1)], 1982-2004; 13.; 1 folder 3" (Box 159)
      - Syria [441.2(334)], 1997-2003; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 162)
      - Turkey [441.2(336)], 1963-2004; 15.; 6 folders 13" (Box 162, Box 163, Box 164)
    - AFRICA
      - Kenya [441.2(251)], 1963-1998; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 151)
      - Nigeria [441.2(238)], 1963-1999; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 151)
      - Somalia [441.2(248)], 1991-1992; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 151)
      - Tanzania [441.2(251)], 1963-1998; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 151)
      - Uganda [441.2(251)], 1963-1998; 5.; 1 folder 3" (Box 151)
      - South Africa [441.2(255)], 1982-2003; 6.; 2 folders 7" (Box 152)
    - EASTERN EUROPE
      - East Bloc [441.2(3)], 1964-2003; 1.; 13 folders 51" (Box 100, Box 101, Box 102, Box 103)
      - East Germany West Germany, Trade relations [441.2(3)A], 1973-1997; 2.; 1 folder 5" (Box 104)
      - PHARE operations [441.2(3)b], 1989-2003; 3.; 2 folders 8" (Box 105)
      - East Central Europe Temporary Tariff Quotas [441.2(3)C], 1994-2003; 4.; 2 folders 9" (Box 105)
      - PHARE Tender Bids [441.2(3)D], 1994-1996; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 106)
      - Baltic Republics [441.2(39)], 1991-2003; 6.; 2 folders 16" (Box 113)
      - Romania [441.2(63)], 1969-2003; 7.; 2 folders 9" (Box 124)
      - Bulgaria [441.2(46)], 1990-2003; 8.; 2 folders 6" (Box 115)
      - Hungary [441.2(54)], 1988-2003; 9.; 1 folder 9" (Box 121)
      - Poland [441.2(61)], 1989-2003; 10.; 1 folder 6" (Box 122)
      - Czechoslovakia [441.2(71)], 1988-1993; 11.; 1 folder 2" (Box 133)
      - Czech Republic [441.2(71.1)], 1993-2003; 12.; 1 folder 4" (Box 134)
      - Slovak Republic [441.2(71.2)], 1993-2003; 13.; 1 folder 3" (Box 134)
    - FORMER SOVIET UNION
      - Soviet Union [441.2(64)], 1986-2003; 1.; 3 folders 13" (Box 124)
      - TACIS [441.2(64)A], 1991-2003; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 125)
      - Commonwealth of Independent States (CIS) [441.2(64.0l)], 1992-1995; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 126)
      - Ukraine [441.2(64.1)], 1992-2003; 4.; 1 folder 4" (Box 126)
      - Turkmenistan [441.2(64.10)], 1998-2000; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 126)
      - Tajikistan [441.2(64.11)], 1999-2003; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 126)
      - Kazakhstan [441.2(64.2)], 1992-2003; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 126)
      - Moldova [441.2(64.3)], 1992-2003; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 126)
      - Kyrgyzstan [441.2(64.4)], 1992-2003; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 126)
      - Belarus [441.2(64.5)], 1995-2002; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 126)
      - Armenia [441.2(64.6)], 1996-2003; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 126)
      - Azerbaijan [441.2(64.7)], 1998-2002; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 126)
      - Georgia [441.2(64.8)], 1996-2003; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 126)
      - Uzbekistan [441.2(64.9)], 1996-2003; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 127)
    - SOUTH EAST EUROPE
      - Albania [44l.2(40)], 1991-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 114)
      - Yugoslavia [441.2(70)], 1964-2003; 2.; 7 folders 30" (Box 130, Box 131, Box 132)
      - Slovenia [441.2(70.1)], 1993-2003; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 133)
      - Macedonia [441.2(70.2)], 1993-2003; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 133)
      - Croatia [441.2(70.3)], 2001-2003; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 133)
    - ASIA
      - Asia [441.2(300)], 1975-2003; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 153)
      - ASEAN [441.2(301)], 1971-2003; 2.; 2 folders 7" (Box 153)